ILR School Department of Collective Bargaining, Labor Law, and Labor History Files /4221
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Department of Collective Bargaining, Labor Law, and Labor History Files
1972-2000
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR). Department of Collective Bargaining, Labor Law, and Labor History
/4221
10 cubic feet
10 linear ft.
Records (documents).
8055089
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Nicole Dardia, June 19, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 04, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Department of Collective Bargaining, Labor Law, and Labor History
8055089
- Annual Reports Extension, 1979-1998. (Box 1)
  - CB, LL, LH Annual Reports, 1979-1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - CB, LL, LM - Pending, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - CB, LL, LH -- Summer Sess. 1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - CB, LL, LH Admin 1988 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - CB, LL, LH Admin 1991 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - CB, LL, LH Adm. Courses Student Evaluations, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - CB, LL, LH, Admin. Executive Staff & Dept. Chairmen, 1985-1988 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - CB, LL, LH Admin Fac. Advisors - 1983 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - CB, LL, LH, Admin - Fac. Rev. - 1990 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - CB, LL, LM Graduate Faculty, 1968-1978 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - CB, LL, LH Adm. Teaching Loads, 1970-1989 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - CB,LL,LH Admin. Review of CB Dept. 1992 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - CB, LL, LH Adm - Review of ILR School, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - CB, LL, LH Adm. Recruitment Faculty 1983 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - CB, LL, LH Admin. Guest Speaker Funds, 1983-1992 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Phillip Beaumont, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - ILR 200 Spring 1990 P. Gerhart (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - CB, LL, LH Admin. Guest Speaker Funds, 1983-1993 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - CB,LL,LH Admin. Visiting Fellows, 1987-1990 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - CB,LL,LH Admin Visiting Faculty, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - CB, LL, LH, Courses General, 1989-1992 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - CB, LL, LH Courses Teaching Assign 1979-81, 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - CB, LL, LH Courses Elective Cred. ILR, 1980-1993 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - CB, LL, LH Courses Required Credit, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - CB, LL, LH, Courses Elective Out of College, 1981-1985 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Credit for Out-of-College Courses, 1973-1982 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Metropolitan Area Temporary Professional Staff, 1979-1998. (Box 2)
  - CB, LL, LH Extension Off-Campus Cred. Progs, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - CB, LL, LH Extension Off-Campus Cred. Progs. 1982 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Mtgs., 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - CB, LL, LH Courses Descriptions (catalog, et.), 1987-1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - CB, LL, LH Staff Prof. Active Burton, John, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - CB, LL, LH, Staff Prof. Crivens Thelma A. (1985-Present) (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - CB, LL, LH, Staff Prof.- Active Cullen, Donald, 1988-1992 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - CB, LL, LH, Staff Prof. Active Doherty, Robert, 1980-1984 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - CB, LL, LH Staff Prof. Active Donovan, Donald, 1981-1989 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - CB, LL, LH Staff Prof. Active Gramm, Cindy, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - CB, LL, LH, Staff Prof. Temporary, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - CB, LL, LH, Staff Prof. Retired, 1981-1990 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Staff: Retired Professional Active Professional- Gold, 1979-1998. (Box 3)
  - CB, LL, LH Staff Prof. Active Korman, Gerd, 1986-1990 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - CB, LL, LH, Staff Prof. Active Ross, Phillip, 1981-1987 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - CB, LL, LH Staff Prof. Active Windmuller, John, 1981-1987 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 1996-1997 Annual Reports (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - 1997-1998 Annual Reports (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Annual Reports 95-96, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - CB, LL, LH, Staff Nonprofessional, 1996-2000 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - CB, LL, LH, Staff Prof. Cook Maria, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - CB, LL, LH, Staff Prof. Active Daniel, Cletus, 1983-1985 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - CB, LL, LH Staff Prof. DeVault, Ileen, 1989-1997 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - CB, LL, LH, Staff Prof., 1980-1990 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Staff, Professional: Gray Cook, 1979-1998. (Box 4)
  - CB, LL, LH, Staff Prof. Gray, Lois, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - CB, LL, LH Staff Prof. Active Gross, James, 1982-1990 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - CB, LL, LH, Staff Prof. Hebdon, Robert, 1994-1996 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Kahn, Larry, 1995-1997 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - CB, LL, LH Staff Prof. Active Katz, Harry, 1986-1990 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - CB, LL, LH, Staff Prof. Kuruvilla, Sarosh, 1990-1996 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - CB, LL, LH, Staff Prof. Active Leiberwitz, Risa, 1985-1997 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - CB, LL, LH, Staff Prof. - Active Lipsky, David, 1981-1987 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - CB, LL, LH, Staff Prof. Active Salvatore, N., 1989-1996 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Sherwyn, David, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Sione, Patrizia (Visitor 94-95), 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - CB, LL, LH, Staff Prof. Stone, Katherine, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - CB, LL, LH - Staff Prof. ACTIVE Turner, Lowell, 1990-1997 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Maria L. Cook, 3 yr. Review (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Staff: Kuruvilla Flynn, 1979-1998. (Box 5)
  - Sarosh Kuruvilla, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Sarosh Kuruvilla, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Robert Hebdon, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Robert Hebdon, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Robert Hebdon, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - ILR 200, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Extra Materials from Hebdon for File, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Teaching Evaluations (scores) (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - R. Hebdon, 1993-1997 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Labor Lawyer Professor Search Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Crain, Marion, 1989-1994 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - DeChiara, Peter, 1988-1994 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Flynn Joan, 1988-1994 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Staff: Young Performance Reviews, 1979-1998. (Box 6)
  - Young, Donna, 1992-1994 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - EXT Assoc. Dean Search, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - EXT Asst. Prof. Labor Studies, 1969-1977 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Adm. ILR Forms Termination Vacation, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Adm. ILR Inventory CB, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Office Aides, 1980-1993 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Xerox - Filing Guide, 1973-1987 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Stenographer 3 Room 288, 1983-1993 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Freeze - CU, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Search - Labor Hist - 1980 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Adm. ILR Forms Guest Travel, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Adm. ILR Forms Printing, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Adm. ILR Forms Research Proj. & Cluster Numbers, 1981-1989 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Labor - Other Countries - Africa, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Clete Daniel's Promotion Dept. Level - SP 1987 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Sarosh Kuruvilla, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Faculty Papers and Vitas, 1979-1998. (Box 7)
  - Sarosh Kuruvilla, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Notice of Appeal, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Risa Lieberwitz, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Prof. Risa Lieberwitz, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Waivers of Rights Under the National Labor Relations Act: Shifting Standards, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Department Review; Lieberwitz, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Lieberwitz; Letters, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Lieberwitz; Miscellaneous, 1988-1990 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Lieberwitz, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Tenure File; Risa L. Lieberwitz, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Lieberwitz; ILR, 1983-1985 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Lieberwitz; ILR, 1987-1989 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Risa L. Lieberwitz Misc., 1989 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Departmental Review; Lieberwitz, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Correspondence Consulting, 1979-1998. (Box 8)
  - Sons and Daughters of Labor, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Cynthia Gramm VITAE, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - "Environmental Determinants of Centralization of the Collective Bargaining Function in American Unions" Gramm, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - "Inflation Uncertainty and strike Activity" Gramm, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - "Learning by Striking: Estimates of the Teetotaler Effect" Gramm, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - "The Determinants of Strike Incidence and Severity: A Micro-Level Study," (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - High Priority/ Departmental, 1979-1989 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Cynthia Gramm, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Cynthia Gramm, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Cynthia Gramm, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Burton/ Departmental for Joyce Orzino/ High, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - CBLLLH - Feb. 12, 1987, 1986-1988 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - CB, LL, LH - Admin. 1979-1988 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - CB, LL, LH Admin. Advisory Council, 1979-1988 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - CB, LL, LH Admin. Dept. Chairmen - Univ., 1982 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - CB, LL, LH Adm. Honors Program, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Promotion and Tenure, 1971-1979 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - CB, LL, LH Adm. Sabbatical Leave, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - CB, LL, LH Adm. Study Lv. (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - CB, LL, LH - Admin. Women's Caucus, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - CB,LL,LH Consulting, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - CB. LL. LH - Administration - Affirmative Action, 1979-1981 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Courses: ILR 499 Faculty Recruitment, 1979-1998. (Box 9)
  - CB,LL,LH Courses ILR 499, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - CB,LL,LH Courses Teaching Assignments 1977-1979 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - CB, LL, LH - Course Off Campus, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - CB, LL, LH Meetings & Minutes 1975-1979 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - CB, LL, LH, EXT - Faculty Compensation, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - CB, LL, LH EXT Off-Campus Credit Programs, 1980-1982 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - CB, LL, LH, Extramural Courses/Teachers, 1976-1979 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - CB, LL, LH - FMCS - Cole Fellowship & Internship, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - CB, LL, LH Recruitment Dean, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - CB, LL, LH Recruitment Faculty 1980-81, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - CB, LL, LH, Search Com. Collective Barg. 1979 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - CB, LL, LH Com. Labor LW 1979 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - CB, LL, LH, Recruitment Faculty 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - CB, LL, LH, Recruitment Faculty Application (Before 1978), 1972-1978 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Seeber, R.L. - 1983 (J.A.Gross' file) (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - CB, LL, LH Staff Prof. Active Seeber, Ronald, 1980-1987 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - CB, LL, LH, Staff Prof. Temp. Fillion, John, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - CB, LL, LH Recruitment Faculty 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Professional Temporary Staff General, 1975-1976, 1979-1998. (Box 10)
  - CB, LL, LH Staff Prof. Temporary Sexton, B., 1979 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - CB, LL, LH Staff Prof. Temp. Shirom, Arie, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - CB, LL, LH Staff Prof. Active Temporary Woodruff, Thomas, 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Cb, LL, LH Staff Prof. Active Finch, Herbert, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - CB, LL, LH Staff Prof. Active Hanslowe, Kurt, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - CB, LL, LH Staff Prof. Active Kennedy, Marian, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - CB, LL, LH Staff Prof. Active Kochan, Thomas, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - CB, LL, LH Staff Prof. Active Keeran Roger, 1975-1980 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - CB, LL, LH Staff Prof. Active Mishel, Larry, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - CB, LL, LH Staff Prof. Active Rehmus, Charles, 1979-1981 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - CB, LL, LH General 1977-1980 (Joyce's cc) (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - CB, LL, LH General 1976-1977 (Joyce's cc) (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - CB, LL, LH - General - 1975-1976 (Joyce's cc) (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Minutes of Meetings, 1974-1976 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Jim Gross - Pending - Search, 1979-1992 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Memorandum, 1974-1989 (Box 10, Folder 16)